Jim Morrison

CV of a UX Designer



Portfolio jimmorrison.io

Email

jim@jimmorrison.io

Phone

07525347461

I'm a multi-discipline UX designer, currently studying a BDes Interaction Design at the Belfast School of Art.

I love working on projects that focus on user interaction; designs that can evoke feeling, producing a happy, more positive experience. I design, develop & play with new technologies, dabbling in digital compositions including audio, graphic and video.

I also lecture part-time, teaching the next generation of students web technologies, design and development at Northern Regional College.

Education

BDes Interaction Design

Ulster University 2016 - Present

Foundation Interactive Design

Northern Regional College 2014 - 2016

HNC Level 5 Business

Belfast Metropolitation 2007 - 2009

Experience

Interactive Media Lecturer

Northern Regional College 2015 - Present

Marketing Executive

Office Interior Solutions 2012 - 2014

Digital Marketing Consultant

Logon NI 2011 - 2012

Information & Data Supervisor

Iron Mountain 2004 - 2011

Skills

HTML	85%
CSS	80%
PHP, JS, MySql	69%
Photoshop	83%
Illustrator	78%
InDesign	76%
After Effects	65%
Premiere	63%
Audition	61%